playunited.com 2016-10-17

# Privacy Policy

**Member Privacy**   
The Account Information supplied during the account creation process is kept strictly confidential for our own purpose. We do NOT share this information with any third party company and/or organization. 

E-mail Addresses are NOT shared with any other organization for commercial or non-commercial purposes. E-mail Addresses will only be used to provide our members with information regarding new updates or promotional material - only if you've subscribed to it.

If you do not want to receive any E-mail from us, please utilize the automatic unsubscribe link at the bottom of our newsletters.

We hate spam just as much as you do so we respect your privacy and therefore will never rent, sell, trade or distribute any information about you. 

**The Information We Collect**   
Becoming a Member will require that you supply personal information about yourself including the following:

• Name   
• Email Address   
• Country

If you wish to signup to our newsletters you only need to provide:

• Name   
• Email Address 

**How we use the information collected?**   
The **Country** is automatically detected by our website & also can be chosen by you manually. We record your country so that we can display relevant casinos that are available to play within your country. Many websites do not do this - leading to many unsatisfied clients when they register and figure out they cannot play at that casino because of where they live. 

**Email and Name** are used in cases where you've opted in to receive our newsletters or special bonus updates. 

Once you become a member a cookie with session data is stored on your computer IF you wish to remain logged into the website when you re-visit it. This information stored in the cookie does not include any personal information therefore it can never be used to compromise your identity. 

**Data Security**   
Play United uses the latest web technologies to ensure all data is safe & secure. Your personal information will be safeguarded by Play United tightly and will never be sold to any mailing lists.

**Contact Us**   
If you should have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy email us at info @ playunited.com
